blinkhealth.com 2016-04-26

# Privacy Policy - Blink Health

Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Terms of Use

Press Info

Effective September 16th, 2015

Blink Health LLC (“Blink”) is committed to maintaining the privacy and security of your personal information, and we appreciate that medical information is particularly sensitive. This Privacy Policy applies to any products or services offered through any Blink website (a “Website”) or Blink mobile application (a “Mobile App”) that links to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Blink Services”). Blink respects the privacy of its healthcare providers (“Providers”), subscribers to the Blink Services (“Members”) and Website visitors (“Visitors”). This Privacy Policy discloses Blink’s information collection and dissemination practices in connection with the Blink Services and applies solely to the information that we collect through the Blink Services. This Privacy Policy does not address personal information that you provide to us in other contexts (e.g., through a business relationship not handled through a Website or Mobile App).

Acceptance of Privacy Policy

By clicking your acceptance of this Privacy Policy, you agree to its terms. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Blink Services. Your continued use of the Blink Services following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.

Personal Information Provided by You

Blink collects your personally identifiable information (“PII”) through the Blink Services when you choose to provide such information, such as when registering to become a Blink member so that you may receive information and updates regarding the Blink Services. PII can include your name, prescription and over-the-counter medications, address, telephone number, e-mail address, Social Security number, date of birth, insurance carrier, pharmacy, and physician.

Blink’s Collection of Your Publicly Available Personal Information

In order to better provide the suite of Blink Services to assist you in managing your healthcare, Blink may request publicly available personal information about you that is maintained by the consumer data companies Acxiom and/or LexisNexis or other similar services. This publicly available personal information is used by Blink to verify your identity in online transactions and to aid in tailoring the Blink Services to your needs.

By agreeing to Blink’s [Terms of Use](https://www.blinkhealth.com/terms), you agree to appoint Blink as your agent for certain purposes, including obtaining your medical information from pharmacies and pharmacy benefit managers (“PBMs”) in order to provide the Blink Services. Please read the “Appointment of Blink as Your Agent” section of the Terms of Use carefully in order to understand Blink’s ability to collect your medical information on your behalf.

Blink’s Use of Personal Information

 _Providing the Blink Services._ Blink will use your PII only to address your requests for information, products or services or in connection with providing you the Blink Services. Specifically, Blink will use your PII to provide the following Blink Services: (i) obtaining your medical information, including protected health information (“PHI”) subject to the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (“HIPAA”), from your physicians, pharmacies, insurance providers and pharmacy benefit managers (collectively, “Healthcare Providers”), (ii) finding lower prices for your healthcare, (iii) negotiating on your behalf with manufacturers and service providers to lower your healthcare expenses, (iv) finding coupons and discounts that may reduce the cost to you of your healthcare, (v) scheduling physician and telemedicine appointments, (vi) assisting you in submitting claims for medical services to your insurer, (vii) arranging for expedited pickup of your prescription drugs using delivery services, (viii) contacting physicians, PBMs, insurance companies, pharmacies and other healthcare providers on your behalf to request medical and insurance coverage information necessary to provide Blink’s services, and (ix) creating other seamless, tailored healthcare experiences.

_Assisting You in Managing Your Healthcare._ Blink may use your PII to assist you in managing your healthcare, including prescriptions and doctor appointments. To do so, Blink may contact you by phone, email or text to (i) find out if you wish to request a prescription refill, (ii) remind you to request a prescription refill, (iii) confirm that a refill request has been submitted, (iv) ask if you wish to transfer a prescription to a different pharmacy, or (v) provide other healthcare services. 

_Marketing by Blink._ Blink may also use your PII to deliver advertisements and marketing communications to you that we believe may be of interest. These advertisements and marketing communications will be delivered solely by Blink. Marketing communications that you receive from Blink may include (i) advertisements for the Blink Services, (ii) advertisements for prescription drugs, (iii) advertisements for telemedicine services providers, and (iv) advertisements for other healthcare services.

Disclosure of Personal Information

Blink will not sell, rent, license, or trade your PII with third parties for their own direct marketing use unless we receive your express consent to do so. Unless you give us permission to do so, Blink will not share your PII other than as specified in this Privacy Policy. Blink will, however, use your PII to find and offer to you coupons and discounts relevant to your healthcare that are offered by third parties.

Because you have appointed Blink as your agent pursuant to the Blink Terms of Use, Blink is authorized to act on your behalf in obtaining your PHI from your Healthcare Providers. As described in this Privacy Policy, Blink is committed to safeguarding the privacy and security of your PII, including medical information, when we use, maintain or transmit that data. However, because Blink is acting on your behalf, it is not a covered entity or business associate subject to HIPAA. Nevertheless, when Blink obtains your medical information while acting on your behalf, we will maintain the privacy and security of that information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy and consistent with the security standards of the HIPAA security regulations.

_Disclosures Related to Providing the Blink Services_  
You acknowledge that any and all information that you provide to Blink may be disclosed to Healthcare Providers in order to provide the Blink Services. For example, Blink may share your PII with a physician for purposes of scheduling a physician or telemedicine appointment. Blink is not responsible for protecting the privacy of your information when it is in the possession of a Healthcare Provider.

_Disclosures to Third Parties Assisting In Our Operations._ Blink may share your PII under confidentiality agreements with other companies that work with, or on behalf of, Blink to provide products and services. These companies may use your PII to assist Blink in its operations. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

_Disclosures Under Special Circumstances._ We may provide information about you to respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process or governmental regulations, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law.

_Business Transfers._ We may share your PII with other business entities in connection with the sale, assignment, merger or other transfer of all or a portion of Blink’s business to such business entity. We will require any such successor business entity to honor the terms of this Privacy Policy.

Automatically Collected Information and Anonymous Information

Each time a visitor uses the Blink Services, Blink collects some information to improve the overall quality of the visitor’s online experience.

_Aggregated Data._ Blink collects aggregate queries for internal reporting and also counts, tracks, and aggregates the visitor's activity into Blink’s analysis of general traffic-flow on the Websites. To these ends, Blink may merge information about you into aggregated group data. In some cases, Blink may remove personal identifiers from PII and maintain it in aggregate form that may later be combined with other information to generate anonymous, aggregated statistical information. Such anonymous, group data may be shared on an aggregated basis with Blink’s affiliates, business partners, service providers and/or vendors; if it does so, Blink will not disclose your individual identity. 

_Web Server Logs and IP Addresses._ An Internet Protocol (“IP”) address is a number that automatically identifies the computer/machine you have used to access the Internet. The IP address enables our server to send you the web pages that you want to visit, and it may disclose the server owned by your Internet Service Provider. Blink may use IP addresses to conduct analyses and performance reviews and to administer the Blink Services.

_Cookies and Web Beacons._ Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to a user’s computer for purposes of storing information about a user’s preferences. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user’s computer. Many websites use cookies as a standard practice to provide useful features when a user visits the website and most web browsers are set up to accept cookies. Blink uses cookies to improve your online experience when using the Blink Services. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, but some portions of the Blink Services may not work properly if you refuse cookies. Some of Blink’s web pages may use web beacons in conjunction with cookies to compile aggregate statistics about Blink Services usage. A web beacon is an electronic image (also referred to as an “action tag,” “single-pixel,” or “clear GIF”) that is commonly used to track the traffic patterns of users from one web page to another in order to maximize web traffic flow and to otherwise analyze the effectiveness of the Blink Services. Some web beacons may be unusable if you elect to reject their associated cookies.

Referral/links

The Blink Services contain links to third-party websites that may offer information of interest. This Privacy Policy does not apply to those websites, and Blink recommends reviewing those websites’ privacy policies individually. 

Security

Blink understands that storing our data in a secure manner is essential. Blink stores PII and other data using industry standard physical, technical and administrative safeguards to secure data against foreseeable risks, such as unauthorized use, access, disclosure, destruction or modification. Although Blink is neither a covered entity nor a business associate subject to HIPAA legal requirements, Blink has implemented data security measures that are consistent with the standards of the HIPAA security regulations. Please note, however, that while Blink has endeavored to create a secure and reliable website for users, the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to or from the Blink Services or via e-mail cannot be guaranteed. 

Your Role in Protecting Your Privacy

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your Blink account password. Never share your Blink password with anyone you don’t want accessing your account. You agree that you will provide access to your password only to insured spouses and/or dependents and you agree any user of your password is bound by the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. It is your sole responsibility to inform Blink of any need to deactivate a password.

Response to “Do Not Track” Signals

Some Internet browsers include the ability to transmit “Do Not Track” signals. Since uniform standards for “Do Not Track” signals have not yet been adopted, Blink does not process or respond to “Do Not Track” signals.

Children's Privacy Protection

_Under Age 13_  
Blink understands the importance of protecting children's privacy in the interactive online world. The Blink Services, including the Websites and the Mobile App, are not designed for, or intentionally targeted at, children under 13 years of age. It is not our policy to intentionally collect or maintain information about anyone under the age of 13. No one under the age of 13 should submit any PII to Blink, a Website and/or the Mobile App.

_Under Age 18_  
Minors under 18 years of age may have the PII that they have provided to Blink through the Blink Services, including a Website or the Mobile App, deleted by sending an email to info@blinkhealth.com requesting deletion. Please note that, while we make reasonable efforts to comply with such requests, deletion of your personal information does not ensure complete and comprehensive removal of that data from all systems. 

Changes

At certain locations on a Website or the Mobile App where information about you may be requested, you are offered the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from Blink. You may also review and request changes to your PII that Blink has collected, including the removal of your PII from Blink’s databases in order to prevent receipt of future communications or to halt receipt of the Blink Services, using any of the following options: 

You can send your request via e-mail to: info@blinkhealth.com 

You can mail your request to the following postal address:

Blink Health LLC "BLINK"  
Attn: Terms of Use/Plan Administrator  
305 West Broadway  
Box 143  
New York, NY 10013  

Policy Updates

This Privacy Policy may be revised from time to time as we add new features and services, as laws change, and as industry privacy and security best practices evolve. We display an effective date on the policy in the upper right corner of this Privacy Policy so that it will be easier for you to know when there has been a change. If we make any change to this Privacy Policy regarding use or disclosure of PII, we will provide advance notice on the Blink Services and in the iTunes App Store, Google Play or Amazon where the Mobile App may be downloaded. Small changes or changes that do not significantly affect individual privacy interests may be made at any time and without prior notice.

Questions?

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or about Blink’s handling of your information, please contact info@blinkhealth.com or 844-442-5465.
